<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">friday</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen" translatable="false">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="leave_app">Do you really want to leave the app?</string>
    <string name="action_leave">Leave</string>
    <string name="nav_main_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_main_history">Usage history</string>
    <string name="nav_project_title" translatable="false">Raspberry PI Android Client</string>
    <string name="main_nav_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="hint_rotate_phone">To use this app, rotate your phone to landscape mode.</string>
    <string name="friday_use_help">To use firday, you have to put this phone into the provided case.</string>
    <string name="nav_history_short">history</string>
    <string name="nav_profile_lower">profile</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen_action" translatable="false">FullscreenActionActivity</string>
    <string name="app_back">Back</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_vr" translatable="false">Edit VR Layout</string>
    <string name="dismiss_btn_seconds">I understood and agree (%d)</string>
    <string name="dismiss_btn">I understood and agree</string>
    <string name="string_time" translatable="false">%s:%s</string>
    <string name="string_time_seconds" translatable="false">%d:%d:%d</string>
    <string name="string_time_expanded" translatable="false">%s, %s:%s</string>
    <string name="string_date_default" translatable="false">%s.%s.%d</string>
    <string name="dialog_warn_title">Please read carefully</string>
    <string name="tou_content">
        Never you use Friday in an enviroment, where the usage of it causes lack of concentration which may lead into mistakes or any other kind dangerous situations.

        friday does not take responsibility for mistakes or any other kind of human failure caused by the use of this product.

        By using this product you agree that this app may contains wrong information when gettings information from our app, widgets etc. We are not responsible for information passed by third-party widgets, or widgets which use third-party sources, such as maps or news.

        We don\'t collect personal data or data from your phone, except in these cases:
            - Bug-reporting: To constantly improve the quality of our service, we will collect data about your app-usage(Which 	  features you use, android version, device name,app version[, the feature which caused the app to crash])
              You can turn off bug-reporting in the app-settings

            - Smart features: The user agreed to the use contacts, location service, camera, microphone, notifications

        By clicking "i understood and agree" you agree that you read the terms of using(above) our privacy policy and accept these.
    </string>
</resources>
